Liam Oflaherty

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Details

253-761-6159

liamoliam2546@gmail.com

Links

GitHub

Portfolio

Arcafeed

FishCat

Skills

JavaScript

Python

HTML

CSS

React

Vue

Angular

PHP

Django

Ruby

Ruby on rails

SCSS

SQL

MySQL

Node.js

Git

GitHub

Adobe Photoshop

Microsoft PowerPoint

Profile

Name: Liam Oflaherty

Address: 1619 7TH ST SW

Phone: 253-761-6159

Email: liamoliam2546@gmail.com

Employment History

Full stack developer, FishCat

APRIL 2022 - PRESENT

Full stack developer at FishCat.org

Full Stack Developer, Arcafeed, Remote

JUNE 2021 - DECEMBER 2021

Full stack developer at Arcafeed. Developed both front and back end from the ground up. As well as developed the payment system. I was also responsible for integrating all of these things together then deploying them.

Full Stack developer, A Mother's Love Daycare, Remote

JANUARY 2022 - APRIL 2022

Created a business website for a local daycare provider.

Education

Computer Science, Pierce College at Puyallup

Bio

Hello my name is Liam, I am a software developer from Seattle Washington with a love for computer science and STEM as a whole. I have plenty of experience working with various languages a few being Javascript, Python, React, Angular, Vue and many more. I also have backend experience with languages like PHP, Laravel and Django.

References

Raunag Mokha from Arcafeed

raunaqmokha66@gmail.com | https://www.arcafeed.com